nothing
I
Oh, I know what I'm supposed to do to
do all I know what I'm supposed to do?.
Don't let it go, don't let it go!.
Fly by the way.
The battle of the world is
not the only one who has hurt,
but it won't be the only one who has hurt.
The sword of the world is not
the only one who has hurt.
Let's start with
the new world.
Oh
I believe.
The future will always be
connected to one another.
We'll see each other!
I won't be the same for you.
Don't forget to fight together?
It's pissed off!
Would you pull it together already?
Why do all your moves suck so much, huh?
That's one for Ace.
Just give it up with the rubber crap.
Or at least learn to fight like
a normal person first. No way!
I was so close!
Just you wait, it's gonna be
awesome when I get it right!
Come on, one more try! Sorry, man.
You know the rules, 100 matches a day.
You can try it tomorrow.
Luffy lost 50 times to both of us.
Knee versus Ace looks like 24 to 26.
Lost by two points. So close!
You just win because you're older!
I'm telling you, when I turn
10, I'm gonna kick your butt!
You do realize we'll be 13 then, right?
Anyway, let's go look
for something to eat.
That looks yummy.
I can eat crocodile every day.
Okay, but make sure he
doesn't eat you this time.
You're lucky you got
swallowed whole before.
Better safe than sorry, huh?
You can't swim, so stay up here and watch.
Crocodile me!
If you don't die, I'm so gonna kill you!
The harsh environment of Mount Grove made
the three boys grow stronger each day.
To the north of their forest playground,
the dirty dealings of Grey
Terminal continued as usual.
And even further north than that, there
was a city with a solid stone wall,
handily keeping the nearby
criminals at arm's length.
The only entrance from the junkyard
below is called the Great Gate.
Twice a day,
mountains of discarded trash from all
over the country are carried through it?
and dumped into Gray Terminal.
Here it comes! Let's go!
Treasure hunting time!
From time to time,
residents of Gray Terminal will enter the
city to sell what they
call recycled goods.
Hey, wait!
What's in that package?
Crocodile skin.
Want it? What?
Go ahead.
Beyond the Great Gate
is a boulevard through
which everyone entering
the city must pass.
It leads to Edgetown.
Edgetown, populated by
thugs and criminals,
lacks the refinement seen
in the rest of the city.
Hey there, buddy.
Need some help with that heavy package?
Hey, answer me when I speak to you.
Buzz off. What?
You're dead!
Gotta pick your targets more carefully.
You might get more than you bargained for.
Aw, dammit, not them! Look out!
No mercy! All right!
In the middle of the city, another
stone wall reaches to the skies.
This one encloses Hightown,
which separates those with noble
blood from their lesser neighbors.
This is the shining
jewel of the Goa kingdom.
Said to be the most beautiful
country in all of the East Blue,
not a hint of trash can
be found on its streets.
Windmill Village can make no such claim.
And although it's technically
a part of the Goa Kingdom!,
the fact is often swept under the rug?
by its more wealthy inhabitants.
Three bowls of ramen.
Thank you for waiting.
Enjoy your meal.
So this is ramen, huh?
Whoa, looks good.
Well, eat it already.
Took the words right out of my mouth!
Seconds, please!
We require seconds!
Three more bowls, boo's taste!
Yes, sir, on the way!
May I come in?
You might want to see this!
Are you sure?
Sir, I think we need to talk.
They found us out!
Yeah, look it!
It's a Dine and Dash!
Catch those criminals!
Wow, ramen sure is good!
I know, right? Worth it!
Criminals?
They're just kids!
Damn it, how did those little
pests sneak through the gate again?
I've had enough of their
antics for a lifetime!
Don't let them get away!
I don't care if they're kids!
They belong in a damn jail!
Did they realize they
were on the fourth floor?
Because that is a long fall!
The window is a mess, but we
lost 26 bowls of ramen too!
Sir, look at this.
Those kids left a weird note.
What is a treasure tab?
Wait.
Sabo?
I can't believe it's him.
Please come back. It's you. You're alive.
Let's go home.
The hell is this?
Are you friends with that old dude, Sabo?
I think he knows you.
He's confusing me with
someone else, that's all.
No!
Sabo, come back!
Sabo.
We will have a visit this spring.
Dogra! Mangra!
What is Goa? A country?
Uh, that's the country we live in.
Mount Grove, Windmill Village, and
Great Terminal are all part of Goa.
Hmph, I knew that.
It must be the end of the world.
I wasn't even sure you could read,
and now you're reading the paper.
Frankly, it's kinda creeping me out. Oh.
Anyway,
they're making a big
deal about this visit,
but it's not like they're gonna haul
their asses all the way to our mountain.
Not that I'd want to see
those pompous bastards anyway.
Celestial dragons?
No thanks.
You're wrong.
I'm not hiding anything.
That's cool, then.
Come on, how stupid can you get?
He's full of it.
Damn it, Sabo.
We can't keep secrets from each other.
So talk!
There's nothing for me to tell you.
You trying to pick a fight
with me, spit it out already!
Okay, okay, just stop killing me!
The son of a noble?
Who is?
I am!
Hmm, so?
If you don't care, then
why didn't you ask me?
The truth is, both my
parents are still alive.
So yeah, I'm not an orphan.
That means I lied about growing
up in Grey Terminal, too.
And that guy who was calling out to me?
That was my dad.
I'm sorry.
I know I've been lying to
you guys for a long time now.
Well, he said he's sorry,
so we gotta forgive him.
I'm not forgiving anyone
till I hear the whole story.
If you're really from a noble family,
why would you want to live
in some crappy junk heap?
Because I ran away from home, that's why.
You understand, don't you, Sabo?
A noble must be a gentleman,
educated, well-mannered, and wise.
And then, when you're older, you can
marry a girl from a royal family.
That will make Mommy and Daddy very happy.
Of course, I'm sure
you'll be very happy, too.
Hello? Hello?
The Lick?
I cannot afford this.
What a mess.
Hey, Dad.
Look at this.
I drew it for you.
Your father is having
a trying day at work.
Sabo, if you have time to draw
this, you have time to study.
Hey, you!
I'm from the royal family, and that
means you have to do everything I say.
Carry me back to my house.
How dare you!
I'm related to the king, and I want
a piggyback ride right now! Stop!
Get off of me!
You nobles think you're so hot, don't you?
This ought to teach you!
My son has royal blood!
I won't stand for you spilling
it on the pavement, you old!
Sabo, tell me you didn't get in a fight
with this boy from the royal family!
Well, kind of.
I mean, he attacked me with
this scary knife, so...
My son can be such a little beast.
I blame myself.
I do hope you aren't hurt.
It's terrible, I know.
Please forgive us.
I assure you he will be
punished severely for this.
I'll do anything I can
to make things right.
Shall we go to the doctor to
make sure your son isn't injured?
Then I realized they love their money,
their property, their status?
but not their son.
If I couldn't marry into a royal
family, I was useless to them.
They tried to teach me culture
and literature and all that stuff.
But I guess I didn't
learn fast enough because
they were always arguing and getting mad.
That family had no place
for someone like me.
I know you guys have it worse, but even
if I had parents, I was still alone.
I heard that you've been sneaking out
behind my back, going goodness knows where.
I shouldn't have to tell you this,
but stay away from Great Terminal
if you know it's good for you.
We nobles are privileged to live in
Hightown with the king and his family.
It's a life the people down
there can only dream of.
By the same token, you do
not belong in their world.
Well, at least the people in Great
Terminal know what it means to be free.
If the nobles in Hightown
didn't spend their
whole lives licking the
boots of the royal family,
Maybe they'd look up and see
that there's more to the world.
Man, I had no idea.
Ace, Luffy, listen.
The three of us, we're
gonna leave this country.
We're gonna sail the
seas and see the world.
And once I've done it all, I'm
gonna write a book for kids like me.
Cause studying is fun when
you're learning about adventure,
and we're gonna have lots of them.
We're gonna be pirates!
You don't gotta tell me.
I'm gonna be a pirate anyway.
I'll be so tough that all the other pirates
and all the marines will bow at my feet.
Everyone in the world will know my name.
That's gonna be the legacy
I leave behind when I die.
I don't care if people hate me.
I don't care if they
wish I'd never been born.
But they won't ignore me.
That's what it means to be
strong, to be a great pirate.
I won't ever lose and
I won't ever run away.
Who cares if the world fears me or respects
me or whatever I'm gonna be a legend?
Then I know what I'm gonna be Tim!
You dork just gotta try
and show me up, don't you?
I don't know if you'll be a king or not.
But you're gonna do something crazy!
I know that much for sure.
We all want to be pirates
together though, don't we?
We're only saving for one ship But what
if all three of us want to be captain?
Damn it, I never thought of that.
Sabo, I always figured you'd
be the navigator on my ship!
You guys are welcome to join my crew?
No thanks!
Well, we'll figure it
out when the time comes.
Maybe we'll leave on one ship
and maybe we'll leave on three.
Oh, you stole that from Dadan, huh?
Let me tell you guys a secret.
All it takes to become
brothers is to share some sake.
Whoa, really?
That's so cool!
We may sail in different seas with
different crews on different ships.
But wherever we go and
whatever adventures we have.
We'll always be brothers and
nobody can take that away.
From now on, we're
honest-to-goodness brothers.
Cheers to that!
Brothers!
Thank you.
¶¶
Give him back, you jerk!
What do you mean, give
him back, you filthy rat?
Sabo is my son,
which means that he's obligated to live
on the path that I have prepared for him.
You should be ashamed, steering him
toward the life of a petty thief.
You're both nothing but wannabe thugs.
Why did you do it? For my money?
Screw your damn money!
You foolish pirate, quit knocking
that kid around so carelessly.
You'll get that delinquent's
disgusting blood on my nice clothes.
Hey, Ace!
Hey, come back here!
Stop this, okay?
Nobody tempted me to do anything.
I only ran away because I wanted to.
I'll be dealing with you later, Sabo.
Take him!
Deal with the other two
however you see fit.
Not a problem, sir.
You've already paid us quite handsomely.
We'll make sure these two
never bother your boy again.
I'll spare you the gory details.
Wait, Blue Jam!
Please don't hurt them!
Call them off, Dad!
I get it! Please stop! Huh?
What do you mean, you get it?
Don't you dare, Sabo!
I'll do whatever you want me to, okay?
I'll live whatever life you've mapped out.
Just please, I'm begging
you, don't hurt my friends?
They've done nothing wrong!
I can't stand this!
Those two are my brothers!
Sabo, no!
Oh?
If that's what you want, then go home!
And promise you'll stop playing
pirate with Lolice in this trash heap?
No!
Don't do it! Shut up, kid!
Damn it, Sabo!
Run away from them!
Luffy and I can take care of ourselves.
This is your life.
You have to be free!
He's right! Don't go!
Are you going to abandon all
your dreams just like that? Sabo!
Sabo!
Hey, Captain, what do you want
us to do with the other ones?
We'll take them back to
the hideout. Yes, sir.
Bastard, untie me!
Come here and fight!
I'm not gonna lose this time!
It must be awful nice to be a noble.
Wouldn't you punks agree?
To them, we're no different than
the piles of garbage we live in.
They just sit back while
we do all the dirty work.
It's a pretty cushy life
your buddy's living, I'd say.
You got no clue what you're talking about!
Pirate life is way better
than being a stupid noble!
Sabo said so himself!
You kids are so hopeless I
can't help feeling bad for you.
Hey, untie their robes in quick.
Yes, sir.
Why do you think a kid from a noble family
ran off to a place like Grey Terminal?
Did you think he just wanted
to make some new friends?
He was mocking you and
all the other people here,
just like adult nobles do
when they're feeling bored.
Real sorry to break it to you.
That boy's no friend of yours.
You're lying.
Sabo would never pull a stunt like that.
He's right.
He said we were brothers.
You heard him.
Yeah, guess so.
Whatever you kids say.
But in any case, you boys aren't going to
bother him or his family anymore, are you?
Because if that's the plan,
I'm afraid I'd have to take you
both out right here and now.
If you really think of
him as your brother,
it'd be best for everyone
to leave him alone.
Leave him alone?
What about our dream?
No!
Sabo told us that he hates Hightown!
Look, if you really care
about this Sabo kid,
then you gotta let him
go live his own life.
You'll understand when you grow up.
Anyway,
until recently I had a
bone to pick with you
after what happened with
Portjami and our money.
But I'm over all that now.
In fact, I'm kind of impressed at
how tough you little punks are.
Which is why I wanted
to ask you something.
It might just be worth your while.
Thanks to you boys, I'm kinda shorthanded.
So, how would you feel
about doing a job for me?
Don't worry.
It's a short, easy gig.
There's actually not really
much danger involved.
On that barrel's a map of Gray Terminal.
You just have to carry packages to the
locations marked on the map with an X.
You interested?
Okay, sure.
What about pay?
My head is tired.
Pulling stuff's no fun
if Sabo's not around.
Just deal with it.
I don't like this either.
I'd much rather find Sabo and rescue
him, but Blue Jam had a point.
We've got to let him live his own life
Look give it some time.
He's gonna be all right,
and if he doesn't like it,
he can always come and join us again
Until that happens.
Let's keep putting
money in the pirate fund
Believe what you want.
It's still not Ace and Luffy's fault.
Quit wasting our time.
Tell us the truth Wait just a minute.
Those scoundrels must have threatened you.
They really have you wrapped
around their fingers.
No, they aren't those
kind of people, okay?
Any noble with a criminal
record to his name
will damage his family's
hard-earned reputation.
You would also be barred
from entering Hightown.
Those two forced you to leave home?
and get involved with their
atrocious acts of violence!
against your better judgment.
Isn't that right, Sabo?
Hmm.
Look here, son.
The fate of your friends in Great
Terminal is in the hand of pirates.
Those pirates work for me.
All I need to do is give the order.
If these slumberettes are that important,
think long and hard about
what you have to do.
You're a smart boy,
born to a great family.
You already know what's right.
You promised me you wouldn't hurt them.
That's the only reason I came back here.
You haven't changed at
all since I ran away.
No one tempted me.
I made every decision by my own free will.
You disappoint me.
I apologize, sir.
I'm so ashamed that I
have such a foolish son.
Surely you understand my dilemma.
Of course.
It must tear you apart inside.
Don't you worry.
I'll take care of all the paperwork.
Welcome back, sir.
Home at last.
Let's go, Sabo.
You've been gone quite some time.
Ah, on second thought, don't
come in yet, you must be filthy.
Hose yourself off in the yard
first, then come in and take a bath.
We're all glad that you're
back home safe, young master.
Oh, goodness!
Is it really you?
You've grown so big!
Hello, Mom.
Now, Stella, say hello
to your brother, Sabo.
Nice to meet you, big brother.
I'm Stella and I'm eight.
What about you?
What the hell?
We adopted him.
He's a promising boy from
another noble family.
For reasons beyond understanding, his
parents suddenly became neglectful.
So far, he's fit in extremely well.
I imagine that if things
don't work out with
you when it's time to choose a successor,
then he would...
No, no, never mind.
I've said too much.
Go and get settled in your room.
You'll resume your
studies tomorrow morning.
Are you going to abandon all
your dreams just like that?
Hey, do you know what I heard?
You're dumb as a brick.
That's what Mama and Papa think,
in case you couldn't guess.
But still, you sure are lucky.
Tomorrow night, they're
taking care of the garbage.
To think had you stayed in
Gray Terminal a day longer?
You'd be dead like the rest of the crooks!
Too bad!
My life would be a lot easier
if you never came back.
But I'm clever enough, so I'll make do.
Hey, Al, stop!
Let go of me or I'll tell
Papa What did you say?
What's going on?
You tell me everything
or I'll beat you up Wait!
Tomorrow, there's going to be a fire!
They're burning gray terminal.
A fire?
That's right You didn't hear about it
because you've been away for so long.
The nobles in Hightown
decided it months ago.
The world government is sending a group of
people to check out all of the East Blue.
They're finally going to arrive and
go a kingdom three days from now.
Rumor has it they have a world
noble, a celestial dragon with them.
People are panicking.
The members of the royal family don't want
him to see all the dirty
parts of this country.
So they made the obvious decision
to burn down Great Terminal.
It's a surefire way to cleanse
this country of all its rubbish.
There's no way they'd just burn
everything down without warning!
Don't joke about something like that!
There's a lot of people
living in Great Terminal.
They can't just torch down their
homes because they feel like it!
Get off of me!
You really are stupid.
Haven't you heard a
single thing I've said?
All the shame of this country.
Tomorrow they're gonna burn it all away.
The people, too?
Hey, wait up!
Where are you going?
You can't jump out the window like that!
Wow, he's a goner.
It's a lie.
It's gotta be.
They can't burn down a place that big.
And someone would have heard.
Soldiers from this afternoon.
Are we sure we're ready for tomorrow?
There can't be any miscalculations.
We're ready on our end, but we're
stuck relying on the pirates.
They have to burn the trash
precisely at the right time.
Don't worry.
Blue Jim and his men
have been placing boxes
of oil and explosives
all over Gray Terminal.
Just like we asked
Blue Jam has a hand in this it must
be true, but why what's in it for him?
Hey Ace, what do you think
Saba's doing? Seriously?
Shut up.
I Thought we had agreed to stop
worrying about him for now.
Okay.
Who knows, this could actually
work out better for him?
Okay, think,
if there was really going
to be a fire tonight,
the people in the town would
be upset about it, right?
Why, good morning?
A good morning to you, sir!
What a beautiful sunny day!
Yes, lovely.
What a relief, guess there's nothing
fishy happening today after all!
I'll walk around for a bit.
Today is windy.
That's true, your majesty,
very windy indeed!
Accidents can happen
easily on a day like this.
Especially wildfires.
How right you are, majesty!
It's quite possible. What?
Sabo snuck out of the house?
He's such an ungrateful brat!
All he cares about is playing
pirate with his friends!
When he should stay at home and study.
Have the police search the entire town.
He couldn't have gotten
very far by himself.
Um, excuse me.
What do you want, kid?
Did you know that there's supposed to
be a fire in Grey Terminal tonight?
Of course I know about the fire.
Why, what's wrong?
Did they cancel it?
He knows.
Tell me, boy, whose family are you from?
So, it's true.
Hold on!
Everyone knows, don't they?
They have from the start.
Look at them. They're smiling.
They don't give a damn about
the people in Great Terminal.
They're happy to see
them burn to the ground.
You know, we've been waiting on you.
Are there any more boxes
you need us to move?
Yeah, and I've got a bigger
job for you later on.
But we'll talk more about that tonight.
Yes, I heard all about the fire.
And you're not worried at all?
Nobody in this town cares what happens?
Nobody in town even thinks
of stopping this thing?
That's admirable of you.
You must have a very kind heart.
But boy, please don't you say a word.
It's important that we
all keep our mouths shut.
Think what would happen if someone outside
of Hightown found out about the plan.
You and I are special.
We come from great noble families.
Calm down.
Ace Luffy there's something
wrong with this town something
wrong with these people They
know people are gonna die.
They're happy people are going to die.
They're sick.
This whole place is sick I
can't stay here any longer.
I have to tell them right now
Today of all days, why is
it so windy? That's him.
That's the missing boy.
Excuse me kid.
You need to come with us
Hey you stop running
The nobles here don't
care who they killed.
They'll burn a whole town alive
just because they don't like it.
You've got to get out of Grey Terminal
and you've got to get out now.
Hold on, Ace!
Luffy, I'm coming!
Why the hell would you want to do that?
Not so loud.
We've got to keep quiet about this.
If anyone finds out, it won't work.
You really are a Moon.
I knew we shouldn't have trusted you.
We've got to hurry and
tell everyone we can, Ace!
I told you to keep quiet.
Hey!
Shut him up!
I'm just following orders, same as you.
In case you didn't guess,
all those boxes you've been lugging
around are filled with explosives.
You get it?
Nothing will survive
that fire, and no one.
But, Blue Jam, don't do it!
Since when did you, Brass, start
giving a damn about other people?
Well, now that you know
about the grand plan...
You're stuck here.
We can't risk letting you go. Sorry.
Actually, there's something I've
been meaning to ask you boys.
So, tell me.
Is it true that you brats are hiding
treasure somewhere around here?
Stupid dog huh?
Hey! Wait!
What's that?
Something weird is
happening in Gray Terminal.
That looks like fire.
Who knew the plan would
turn out to be this fun?
Hey, boss, come quick.
You gotta see this.
All right, what's the big deal? Mr.
Skye, look.
Is that the town?
No, it's closer than that.
I think it's Grey Terminal.
It's on fire.
What's going on?
Where's that smoke coming from?
Grey Terminal has never
caught fire before.
What happened?
Edge Town is too dangerous.
Evacuate immediately.
All residents, please head downtown.
Stay here where it's safe.
We'll take care of the
fire and other citizen.
Everybody, get up!
We gotta escape!
The fire almost has us surrounded.
Where did this mess even come from?
Look, it's no use, man.
Leave it behind and make a run for it.
Crap!
The fire's already gotten to the shore!
The entrance to the forest is burning too!
We're all gonna die! Where do we go?
Say so long to this dump, fellas.
Good riddance!
It'll be easy living from here on out.
Yeah, just like the nobles.
Of course not.
We couldn't care less about the living
garbage stinking up Gray Terminal.
But it makes a good hideout.
The place is huge, plus no
law around to bug us, get it?
I'm aware of that.
But think, if you do this for me,
well, you won't need a hideout.
I have the authority to make you
and your crew Bone Fight nobles.
Really?
You do that for us?
Once this is through, the King
of Goa will give us titles.
We'll live in high-townest nobles.
No more of this trash heap.
Now, let's move.
We're almost done.
And don't worry.
On to the Great Gate.
The military is waiting for us.
Captain, we left those
two brats in the hideout.
Forget them.
They had their chance to join up when
I asked them where their treasure was.
But they blew it fools like
them are gonna live long anyway
Captain the gate is already
closed. It's nothing.
They just don't want other
people to break in and cause
a riot I'm supposed to give
them a sign once we're here.
Then they'll open it up
It's me blue jam.
We're here
Huh hey open the damn gate
Captain, you don't think...
Hey! Come on!
What the hell are you doing?!
This isn't funny!
Open the gate!
We made a deal!
You're supposed to let us
evacuate from this pit!
Quit screwing around and let
us in, you bunch of bastards!
The King made me a promise!
If we burn down a terminal,
he'd make us nobles!
Don't tell me!
The king set us up! That liar!
Damn it!
Did you hear?
They found out who started the fire.
It was some pirate named
Blue Jam from Grey Terminal.
How despicable.
A criminal turning on his own men.
I bet he was trying to
keep the world government's
observers away so he could
keep on terrorizing people.
Gosh, what an evil pirate.
It's way too hot, Ace!
I think I'm gonna melt!
Oh, you are! Damn!
Why did Blue Jam rope us into this mess?
We can't get away!
I don't want to die!
If you don't stop
complaining, I'll kill you!
It's not that hot!
I'm burning!
I mean, this isn't so bad!
It's all over the place!
I can barely breathe!
I mean, I'm cool!
The fire will kill us all!
We're gonna be fine! Don't worry.
We'll live. Somehow.
Hey, are you nuts?
You're going the wrong way!
Open the gate now!
What are you talking about?
Don't, brat!
Go home!
Luffy! Ace! Run!
Let go, brat!
Stay away from the lock.
Open the gate.
Stop.
No.
Why don't you be a good
kid and get out of here?
Don't give us any more trouble.
I'm sorry, guys.
What happened to you, boy?
Who's there?
Whoever you are, listen, the nobles
are the ones behind this fire.
You gotta believe me.
Hightown wreaks worse than
Great Terminal ever did.
The people act civilized, but on
the inside, they're all rotten.
They only care about making themselves
look good no matter what it takes.
I can't stay here.
If I do, then I'll never be free.
I'm ashamed of being born noble.
I hate myself.
Go, Kingdom.
Look what you've done to this child.
How you've turned him against you.
I know how you feel.
I was born in this country, too.
But I alone do not have the
power to change this world.
And maybe I never will.
But at least...
At least you're actually
listening to me, aren't you?
Of course I am, and I'll never forget.